<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UBC Integrated Engineers</title>
    <description>Student run website of the UBC Integrated Engineers. This site is a resource for current students, prospective students, alumni and industry members.
<<<<<<< HEAD
</description>
    <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://integratedengineers.ca/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2016 09:29:14 -0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2016 09:29:14 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>President&#39;s Update for November 16 2015</title>
=======
</description>
    <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://integratedengineers.ca/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2015 10:51:42 -0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2015 10:51:42 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>President&#39;s Update for November 30 2015</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are your updates for the last week of school! Stay strong, you’re almost there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;e-week-teams&quot;&gt;1. E-Week Teams&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jesse, our E-Week rep, has posted some preliminary teams on the IGEN Facebook group. The poll is the top pinned post. Please sign up for these groups, as they are an awesome way to use your engineering skills in a fun competition and represent your department!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/groups/ubcigen/?fref=ts&quot;&gt;Facebook Event&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;first-aid-courses&quot;&gt;2. First Aid courses&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IGEN is considering bringing in an instructor to teach emergency first aid on Saturday or Sunday in the second week of January. We will hold sessions on both days if there is enough interest. The session is 8 hours and will cost $85. There will be sign up sheets in the clubroom for both days. Please sign up on one of the days to express your interest. A minimum of 15 people is required per session, so if we have less than 15 on a day, then we may combine groups and have one session.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks everyone, and enjoy the week!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2015/11/30/Presidents-Update-November-30/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2015/11/30/Presidents-Update-November-30/</guid>
        
        
        <category>president-update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>President&#39;s Update for November 23 2015</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Good afternoon,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apologies for the late email today. Here are the weekly updates:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;krispy-kreme-fundraiser&quot;&gt;1. Krispy Kreme Fundraiser&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Donuts are being sold this week until Thursday in the Kaiser Atrium! 
We will be setting up a booth in the Kaiser Atrium from November 23  - 26 (11 am - 2 pm everyday) and will be selling Krispy Kreme donuts for cheap:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$10/dozen, $1/single donut&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Come out and support our department buy buying some delicious treats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;igen-jackets&quot;&gt;2. IGEN Jackets&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you to all who signed up to purchase a jacket. Due to the size of our order they will not be finished until January. Thus, hold tight for payment options and information, as well as expected pickup dates. Thanks for your patience!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;eus-football-tournament&quot;&gt;3. EUS Football Tournament&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IGEN had to two teams playing this past Sunday in the EUS Flag Football event. Both teams played very well and represented the department with pride. Big shout out to Tanya Bennet, our sports rep for her organization and Alex Hutchinson, EUS VP Student Life for making the whole tournament a reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;igen-general-meeting&quot;&gt;4. IGEN General Meeting&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you to all who came to the General Meeting last friday. Some excellent discussion took place surround e-week and the IGEN Council’s performance up to this point. As we did not have time to complete our goals discussing future events and initiatives you can expect some polls to appear in the near future on the IGEN facebook pages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks everyone, and have a fantastic week. This week our photo shows some alternative but no less important applications of engineering knowledge; letting this little cutie walk again!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2015/11/23/Presidents-Update-November-23/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2015/11/23/Presidents-Update-November-23/</guid>
        
        
        <category>president-update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>President&#39;s Update for November 16 2015</title>
>>>>>>> 80488ad8c7e5dd628cfdfaa3d8288ac9b4689156
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some very important updates below, so please read through today!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;igen-general-meeting&quot;&gt;1. IGEN General Meeting&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Integrated Engineering Council will be hosting a General Meeting for all students on Friday, November 20th, from 12:00 - 2:00 PM in CEME 1202. The goals of this meeting are to gain feedback regarding council activities up to this point, and have students discuss plans for next semester. Also discussed will be classes and curriculum, e-week consultation done in conjunction with the EUS, and assorted other IGEN related topics. Refreshments will be provided. Come and have a say in how your program functions!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;igen-jackets&quot;&gt;2. IGEN jackets&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IGEN jackets are available to order! Here are the details:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Price: $110-$120 depending on how many we sell, so get your friends out!
Sizing: XS to XL, men’s and women’s
Colour: Slate for Men, Platinum or Black for Women&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To try on sizing we have all of the sizes available in the IGEN clubroom until Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please fill out the following survey to order your jacket! We will detail payment options as soon as we have a final number on the orders. Please note orders are due by Wednesday Nov 18th at 12 noon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://survey.ubc.ca/s/igen-jacket-signup/&quot;&gt;IGEN Jacket Order Form&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;krispy-kreme-fundraiser&quot;&gt;3. Krispy Kreme fundraiser&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Krispy Kreme Fundraiser - Help Wanted!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IGEN is growing in numbers each year and we need money to help cover costs for our shop supplies, clubroom, student affairs, and industry outreach. We will be setting up a booth in the Kaiser Atrium from November 23  - 26 (11 am - 2 pm everyday) and will be selling Krispy Kreme donuts for cheap:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$10/dozen, $1/single donut&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Help booth, sell donuts and spread the word about IGEN! If you got 30mins to spare, or even more, help would be greatly appreciated! Sign up sheet will be posted on the bulletin in the clubroom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Invite your friends to the facebook event (and check our new IGEN logo!):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/1046686905381749/&quot;&gt;Facebook Event&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For questions, email Jael at igentreasurer@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you all, and we’ll see you this Friday at the General Meeting!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2015/11/16/Presidents-Update-November-16/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2015/11/16/Presidents-Update-November-16/</guid>
        
        
        <category>president-update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Meet an IGENeer - Jesse Macht</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; src=&quot;https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/12440671/10349967/4125caa2-6cf6-11e5-950e-95635269af20.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hello, my name is Jesse Macht and I am in my fourth year of Integrated Engineering. I am interested in fluid dynamics and controls engineering, so I have taken courses related to these interests through the Mechanical and Electrical departments, respectively. I have worked with design project teams and a local start up on the development of UAV technology for remote sensing applications in industry. I have also been involved in academic research into the lightweight alloys used for modern automotive and energy applications, both at UBC and McMaster University in Hamilton, Ontario.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Besides the academic and industry work I am involved in, I am very invested in engaging Integrating Engineering students on the social side of their degree experience. This year I am the E-Week representative for the Integrated Engineering Council and I am working with both the EUS and the Council to reimagine how we engage socially through E-Week events and activities. Please do not hesitate to contact me regarding E-Week, any of my academic or industry work, or about the IGEN degree in general. I would love to speak with you!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/meet-an-igeneer/2015/11/16/Meet-an-IGENeer-Jesse-Macht/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/meet-an-igeneer/2015/11/16/Meet-an-IGENeer-Jesse-Macht/</guid>
        
        
        <category>meet-an-igeneer</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>President&#39;s Update for November 9 2015</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Good morning,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are a couple important announcements for the coming week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;krispy-kreme-fundraiser&quot;&gt;1. Krispy Kreme Fundraiser&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Krispy Kreme Fundraiser - Help Wanted!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IGEN is growing in numbers each year and we need money to help cover costs for our shop supplies, clubroom, student affairs, and industry outreach. We will be setting up a booth in the Kaiser Atrium from November 23  - 26 (11 am - 2 pm everyday) and will be selling Krispy Kreme donuts for cheap:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$10/dozen, $1/single donut&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Help booth, sell donuts and spread the word about IGEN! If you got 30mins to spare, or even more, help would be greatly appreciated! Sign up sheet will be posted on the bulletin in the clubroom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Invite your friends to the facebook event (and check our new IGEN logo!):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/1046686905381749/&quot;&gt;Facebook Event&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For questions, email Jael at igentreasurer@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;lunch-around-the-world&quot;&gt;2. Lunch Around the World&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The EUS on November 20th is hosting an event celebrating multiculturalism and food, two things we can all get behind! If someone wants to create an IGEN team and cook some awesome food, signup and details can be found below. Please note the deadline is November 11th for signup!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/1515636585425788/&quot;&gt;Facebook Event&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ubcengineers.ca/events/social/lunch-around-the-world/&quot;&gt;EUS Website and Signup&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you all for your attention, and have a great week!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2015/11/09/Presidents-Update-November-09/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2015/11/09/Presidents-Update-November-09/</guid>
        
        
        <category>president-update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>President&#39;s Update for November 2 2015</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Good morning,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are a few updates for you all:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;academic-consulatation&quot;&gt;1. Academic Consulatation&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This evening all of the year reps and our VP Academic will be representing the department at the EUS Grand Council. There we will be providing feedback regarding our courses and areas for improvement. If you have any constructive feedback regarding our courses and changes you would like to see, please let any of the mentioned people above know, comment on the related Facebook posts, or reply to this email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;grad&quot;&gt;2. Grad&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have not yet had your ring sized or paid you gown deposit, please contact Cobi immediately. Also if you did not get your grad photos taken during the set aside blocks you must call Evangelos Photography and arrange your own appointment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;bulletin-board&quot;&gt;3. Bulletin Board&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to Hailey, we have a new bulletin board in the clubroom! The top portion is to be used by IGEN Council for updates, whereas the bottom portion is or you, our students, to make announcements to the department at large. Any inappropriate language or content  will be removed without notice, and after an event has passed the poster will be removed unless otherwise notified.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2015/11/02/Presidents-Update-November-02/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2015/11/02/Presidents-Update-November-02/</guid>
        
        
        <category>president-update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IGEN CEO Speaker Series: Darby Kreitz</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; src=&quot;/images/DarbyKreitz1.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Darby Kreitz addressing IGEN students&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IGEN 340 hosted renowned entrepreneur Darby Kreitz for a CEO Speaker Series talk.
The event took place in Frank Forward 303.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Darby Kreitz is the CEO of Allnorth Consultants Ltd, a company with just 4 people in 1995 to over 550 people today. Kreitz gave a talk on his background, his leadership style and the importance of choosing a good team to work with. A highlight from his talk was how he chooses “&lt;strong&gt;Attitude over Aptitude&lt;/strong&gt;”: Insisting that while it is important to have good technically minded people on the team, it is even more important that people can fit well together and work as a unit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; src=&quot;/images/DarbyKreitz2.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Darby Kreitz addressing IGEN students&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He proposes his famous “&lt;strong&gt;four hour pickup truck test&lt;/strong&gt;” as a way to hire people, saying that when you want someone on the team, think about whether you can enjoy a 4 hour long pickup truck ride with them. If the answer is no, you probably don’t want to work with them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IGEN is grateful to Mr Darby Kreitz for presenting today and Mr Mark Dance, IGEN 340 instructor, for facilitating the CEO Speakers Series.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; src=&quot;/images/DarbyKreitz3.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Darby Kreitz addressing IGEN students&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/ceo-speaker-series/2015/10/29/IGEN-CEO-Speaker_Series-Darby-Kreitz/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/ceo-speaker-series/2015/10/29/IGEN-CEO-Speaker_Series-Darby-Kreitz/</guid>
        
        
        <category>ceo-speaker-series</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>President&#39;s Update for October 26 2015</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Happy Monday!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Super short updates this week…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;grad-photos&quot;&gt;1. Grad Photos&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For grads who have not yet taken their photos yet, the last official IGEN session is tomorrow from 9am to 6pm. If you wish to sign up for this time slot, please call Evangelos ((604) 731-8314) and schedule a time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After tomorrow, you will need to schedule a photo session yourself. UBC requires that grad photos must be done as a requirement to graduate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;tuition-consultation&quot;&gt;2. Tuition Consultation&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The university is raising international tuition drastically. This has significant ramifications for all students, and is an important moment in the school’s history. Be part of the discussion by attending a information session and have your voice heard!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/1492184164410796/&quot;&gt;Facebook Events &amp;amp; Dates&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;electrical-shop-access&quot;&gt;3. Electrical Shop Access&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Due to feedback from the student body we have changed the policy on the electrical shop: from now on all IGEN students have access to the space with their key card. Please note that should any tools go missing or the space become cluttered this decision will be reversed. Thanks for your co-operation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2015/10/26/Presidents-Update-October-26/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2015/10/26/Presidents-Update-October-26/</guid>
        
        
        <category>president-update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>President&#39;s Update for October 19 2015</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Good morning everyone!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Short list of updates for today to give you the time to do #1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;vote&quot;&gt;1. Vote&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VOTE 
 VOTE
  VOTE
   VOTE&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Much of the world doesn’t have the privilege to contribute to the choice of who leads their nation. Take this opportunity to have your say and be part of the bigger picture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;krispy-kreme-fundraiser&quot;&gt;2.Krispy Kreme Fundraiser&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re having a Krispy Kreme fundraiser! Help IGEN raise funds for our industry outreach, club room and student affairs by boothing in Kaiser on Oct 26 - 28th anytime between 11-3pm. Even if it’s just 30 mins or a couple of hours, your help is greatly appreciated :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please email Jael at lumbajael@gmail.com with your name, phone number, and date &amp;amp; time of availability to booth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;sports&quot;&gt;3. Sports&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IGEN came third at the EUS Ultimate Tournament! Big thanks to Lance Burnett for organizing our team, and IGEN’s own Alex Hutchinson for organizing the event!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;social-night&quot;&gt;4. Social Night&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Friday (October 23rd) starting at 5PM come out to Koerner’s on campus and enjoy a drink with other Integrated Engineers. This is a great way to take the load off of midterms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/1627051410881254/&quot;&gt;Facebook Event&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;project-forum&quot;&gt;5. Project Forum&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This will take place October 24th, at 1PM in the IGEN Clubroom. This is an opportunity for groups to outline and discuss their projects with each other for feedback, as well as to give the other students an idea of what they will be working on for the year. Need help with a certain topic related to your project? Chances are someone in IGEN will be able to help. This is also a great opportunity for the 2nd years to get an idea of what kind of projects are to be expected!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/877829872270229/&quot;&gt;Facebook Event&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;thanks-for-your-attention-have-a-great-election-monday&quot;&gt;Thanks for your attention! Have a great election Monday.&lt;/h3&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2015/10/19/Presidents-Update-October-19/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2015/10/19/Presidents-Update-October-19/</guid>
        
        
        <category>president-update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IGEN is looking for a media team</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; src=&quot;https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1417577354685-3ab67e9716a3?q=80&amp;amp;fm=jpg&amp;amp;w=600&amp;amp;fit=max&amp;amp;s=1941c278eb1c4c1edbd21330af2013d9&quot; alt=&quot;media&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hello IGENeers! My name is Darshan Soni and I am your webmaster. I want to welcome you to our brand new website. Stay tuned here as we get a new logo and brand identity over the course of this term. This site is a great tool for you to access information on what’s happening in IGEN.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;would-you-like-to-be-a-part-of-the-new-igen-media-team&quot;&gt;Would you like to be a part of the new IGEN media team?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The IGEN students club is in the process of revamping all it’s media: website, photo collection, blogs and publications. Over the next few months, this website will grow into a comprehensive hub for all IGEN material. The aim is to be a good student resource that lists information, showcases our projects and appeals to both prospective students and industry members to show off IGEN to the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, this requires a team effort and so we are looking for budding photographers, bloggers and media fans in general. If you’d like to get involved in creating content for the website, &lt;strong&gt;please&lt;/strong&gt; get in touch with me as soon as possible. Good photography will allow us to get a record of you beauties at all our events, bloggers will release updates that keep our students tuned in to whats happening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;whats-in-it-for-you&quot;&gt;What’s in it for you?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well apart from the fact that you’re contributing to the IGEN brand refreshment and making the club even more accessible, there are a few more pros you get by joining the media team:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Develop your photography / blogging skills by getting more exposure and experimentation space with this website.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Learn awesome skills with HTML, JavaScript, SASS and the Bootstrap Framework.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add this exciting project to your resume.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Grow with the project as you go through your degree.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-much-involvement-is-there&quot;&gt;How much involvement is there?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The involvement will depend on the roles you take up and how you wish to work. IGEN wants to empower it’s students and give them the creative space to develop this space further. Any contributions are welcome and you can mould your roles to what you’d like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;alright-lets-do-this&quot;&gt;Alright! Let’s do this!&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re interested, contact me with a facebook message or email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;alert alert-info&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Email address: site@integratedengineers.ca&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Darshan Soni&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IGEN Webmaster&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/hiring/2015/10/19/IGEN-Media-Team_Hiring/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/hiring/2015/10/19/IGEN-Media-Team_Hiring/</guid>
        
        
        <category>hiring</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
