<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Your awesome title</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>http://yourdomain.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://yourdomain.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2015 16:23:32 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2015 16:23:32 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>President&#39;s Update for October 19 2015</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Good morning everyone!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Short list of updates for today to give you the time to do #1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;vote&quot;&gt;1. Vote&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VOTE 
 VOTE
  VOTE
   VOTE&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Much of the world doesn’t have the privilege to contribute to the choice of who leads their nation. Take this opportunity to have your say and be part of the bigger picture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;krispy-kreme-fundraiser&quot;&gt;2.Krispy Kreme Fundraiser&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re having a Krispy Kreme fundraiser! Help IGEN raise funds for our industry outreach, club room and student affairs by boothing in Kaiser on Oct 26 - 28th anytime between 11-3pm. Even if it’s just 30 mins or a couple of hours, your help is greatly appreciated :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please email Jael at lumbajael@gmail.com with your name, phone number, and date &amp;amp; time of availability to booth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;sports&quot;&gt;3. Sports&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IGEN came third at the EUS Ultimate Tournament! Big thanks to Lance Burnett for organizing our team, and IGEN’s own Alex Hutchinson for organizing the event!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;social-night&quot;&gt;4. Social Night&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Friday (October 23rd) starting at 5PM come out to Koerner’s on campus and enjoy a drink with other Integrated Engineers. This is a great way to take the load off of midterms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/1627051410881254/&quot;&gt;Facebook Event&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;project-forum&quot;&gt;5. Project Forum&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This will take place October 24th, at 1PM in the IGEN Clubroom. This is an opportunity for groups to outline and discuss their projects with each other for feedback, as well as to give the other students an idea of what they will be working on for the year. Need help with a certain topic related to your project? Chances are someone in IGEN will be able to help. This is also a great opportunity for the 2nd years to get an idea of what kind of projects are to be expected!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/877829872270229/&quot;&gt;Facebook Event&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;thanks-for-your-attention-have-a-great-election-monday&quot;&gt;Thanks for your attention! Have a great election Monday.&lt;/h3&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/president-update/2015/10/19/Presidents-Update-October-19.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/president-update/2015/10/19/Presidents-Update-October-19.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>president-update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IGEN is looking for a media team</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; src=&quot;https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1417577354685-3ab67e9716a3?q=80&amp;amp;fm=jpg&amp;amp;w=600&amp;amp;fit=max&amp;amp;s=1941c278eb1c4c1edbd21330af2013d9&quot; alt=&quot;media&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hello IGENeers! My name is Darshan Soni and I am your webmaster. I want to welcome you to our brand new website. Stay tuned here as we get a new logo and brand identity over the course of this term. This site is a great tool for you to access information on what’s happening in IGEN.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;would-you-like-to-be-a-part-of-the-new-igen-media-team&quot;&gt;Would you like to be a part of the new IGEN media team?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The IGEN students club is in the process of revamping all it’s media: website, photo collection, blogs and publications. Over the next few months, this website will grow into a comprehensive hub for all IGEN material. The aim is to be a good student resource that lists information, showcases our projects and appeals to both prospective students and industry members to show off IGEN to the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, this requires a team effort and so we are looking for budding photographers, bloggers and media fans in general. If you’d like to get involved in creating content for the website, &lt;strong&gt;please&lt;/strong&gt; get in touch with me as soon as possible. Good photography will allow us to get a record of you beauties at all our events, bloggers will release updates that keep our students tuned in to whats happening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;whats-in-it-for-you&quot;&gt;What’s in it for you?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well apart from the fact that you’re contributing to the IGEN brand refreshment and making the club even more accessible, there are a few more pros you get by joining the media team:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Develop your photography / blogging skills by getting more exposure and experimentation space with this website.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Learn awesome skills with HTML, JavaScript, SASS and the Bootstrap Framework.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add this exciting project to your resume.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Grow with the project as you go through your degree.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-much-involvement-is-there&quot;&gt;How much involvement is there?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The involvement will depend on the roles you take up and how you wish to work. IGEN wants to empower it’s students and give them the creative space to develop this space further. Any contributions are welcome and you can mould your roles to what you’d like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;alright-lets-do-this&quot;&gt;Alright! Let’s do this!&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re interested, contact me with a facebook message or email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;alert alert-info&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Email address: site@integratedengineers.ca&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Darshan Soni&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IGEN Webmaster&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/hiring/2015/10/19/IGEN-Media-Team_Hiring.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/hiring/2015/10/19/IGEN-Media-Team_Hiring.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>hiring</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The New IGEN Site</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; src=&quot;https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1429051883746-afd9d56fbdaf?fit=crop&amp;amp;fm=jpg&amp;amp;h=675&amp;amp;q=80&amp;amp;w=1375&quot; alt=&quot;Website Coding&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the new IGEN site! 
The site was redesigned with our students, alumni and prospective students in mind. In the last few years, a lot of effort went into creating a site and collecting resources for students online. This spawned our famous Google Drive, the mentorship program and online forms. We tip our hats off to those who invested their time and efforts into it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, after some time it was evident that IGEN needed a facelift. We are now a well established stuent club and our growth was being hampered by the lack of a cohesive, student run website. This summer, work has been done to rebuild the site. Although the framework is now complete, the new site depends on &lt;strong&gt;you&lt;/strong&gt; to contribute and build it so that we have a continuously growing student-centred information base that stands the test of time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to IGEN, welcome to the new integratedengineers.ca site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For any questions on site management, comments and complaints please feel free to contact the webmaster, Darshan Soni. You can email in at site@integratedengineers.ca&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Darshan Soni,
Webmaster&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/site/2015/09/24/the-new-igen-site.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/site/2015/09/24/the-new-igen-site.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>site</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
