<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UBC Integrated Engineers</title>
    <description>Student run website of the UBC Integrated Engineers. This site is a resource for current students, prospective students, alumni and industry members.
</description>
    <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://integratedengineers.ca/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 16:42:25 -0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 16:42:25 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>LumenLock</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; src=&quot;/images/LumenLock.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;LumenLock is an integrated medical dressing designed to improve the quality of care for patients who have central venous or peripherally inserted central catheters. Existing medical dressings fail to adequately secure central lines and are not waterproof, often leading to skin irritation due to frequent changes. LumenLock holds the line close to the body and forms a waterproof barrier over the catheter exit site. As a result, patients are less likely to accidentally pull out their lines and fewer dressing changes are required. LumenLock will be sold directly to hospitals, providing a more comfortable, time saving and cost efficient solution. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Team Members&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Gabriel Lessard-Kragen&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Elizabeth Wicks&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ben Blair&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Nick Geddes&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ashley Anderson&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sarah Moug&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/igen-project/2016/02/10/LumenLock/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/igen-project/2016/02/10/LumenLock/</guid>
        
        
        <category>IGEN-Project</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Levee Health Monitoring System</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;
Levee failures are frequent and have catastrophic social, economic, and environmental consequences. What if we could catch shifts in the levee before disastrous failure occurs? The levee health monitoring system does just this by alerting field workers to changes in a levee&#39;s three primary modes of failure: seepage, sliding, and erosion. This data is transmitted to a base station, allowing field workers to move beyond the insufficient visual inspections that are currently used in industry.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Team Members&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Katalin Sandor Johansen&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sara Flanagan&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Kieran Bjornson&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Nate Croft&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/igen-project/2016/02/10/Levee-Health-Monitoring-System/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/igen-project/2016/02/10/Levee-Health-Monitoring-System/</guid>
        
        
        <category>IGEN-Project</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chilly</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; src=&quot;/images/Chilly.jpg&quot; style=&quot;max-height:200px;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A temperature sensor that allows cafes and restaurants to automate and monitor their food safety. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Team Members&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Rhea Sideris,&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Janyce Archutick&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Alex Hutchinson&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/igen-project/2016/02/10/Chilly/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/igen-project/2016/02/10/Chilly/</guid>
        
        
        <category>IGEN-Project</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IGEN Self Branding Event</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;IGEN will be organizing a self-branding event to help anyone looking for feedback on resumes, cover letters, LinkedIn profiles or other essential professional resources. Bring your documents with you to the session to receive helpful tips and feedback from your peers!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have many students who have obtained placements at high level firms such as Tesla, Microsoft, Kiewit, Trane, as well as various research and international opportunities. Come learn from their experience and tailor your brand and materials to have the same success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See the facebook event &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/1695228674051828/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/event/2016/01/27/IGEN-Self-Branding-Event/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/event/2016/01/27/IGEN-Self-Branding-Event/</guid>
        
        
        <category>event</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>President&#39;s Update for January 25 2016</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello all,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope you’re all having a wonderful Monday and are getting psyched up for e-week! Sorry for the long list, but &lt;strong&gt;please read everything here, there is important stuff.&lt;/strong&gt; Without any further ado, here are your updates:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;igen-industry-night&quot;&gt;1. IGEN Industry Night&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The IGEN Project Showcase will be held on April 6th, in the West Atrium of the Life Science Centre. The purpose of this event is to showcase your year long projects, and the IGEN program to professors, parents, and members of Industry. If would like to invite any members of industry, professors or your parents please follow the link below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1Fkmx8XejUMCXYncjDd-y5PuJqL6lJNO34NexxZtli3Q/viewform&quot;&gt;Google Form&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;e-week-signup&quot;&gt;2. E-week signup&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IGEN! E-Week is almost upon us! Please sign up for events on the following google doc. There are events for everyone, so get a group of friends together and go for it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/folderview?id=0B7XREd5s2s9ob1ZWSzhPV3RWajg&amp;amp;usp=drive_web&quot;&gt;E-Week Signup Sheet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the social events, put your name down for the ones you’re interested in so that you can see which of your friends are interested in going! This year IGEN has a great opportunity to not only fight for the the title of E-Week champs, but also to put our best foot forward as the brightest up-and-coming program in the faculty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;old-red-new-red&quot;&gt;3. Old Red New Red&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This event is getting a huge face-lift this year, so you need to sign-up in advance! I highly recommend you take this opportunity to network with alumni.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/1515702418726437/&quot;&gt;Facebook Event and Sign-up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;engineers-ball&quot;&gt;4. Engineers Ball&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This event also has a seperate signup. Come out and celebrate the end of e-week with the most formal event of the year! Mre details can be found below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/610760795729347/&quot;&gt;Facebook Event and Sign-Up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;pre-e-week-party&quot;&gt;5. Pre E-week party&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friday, January 29th will be IGEN’s Pre-E-Week party! We’ll be getting getting into the E-Week spirit with tryouts for Boat Races and Foosball. Beer and snacks will be provided for the tryouts! The event will start at 4pm and take place in our clubroom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/433342116875290/&quot;&gt;Facebook Event&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;iron-ring-information-session&quot;&gt;6. Iron Ring information session&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The info session will be held on Feb 25th, 1:30-2:30pm at the Norm Theatre in the Old SUB.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the sessions Camp 5 Wardens will provide valuable information regarding procedure at the Ceremony and the history and tradition of the Iron Ring. Attendance is mandatory;  and anyone who is unable to attend a Briefing Session due to a legitimate critical alternate commitment only, must appoint a class-mate to take notes on their behalf.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Schedule of events:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Event&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;1:30 pm&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Students arrive at the Norm Theatre&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;1:45 pm&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;All students seated / presentation starts&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;2:15 pm&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Presentation finished, up to 15 minutes for Q &amp;amp; A for students&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;2:30 pm&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Students start to clear out.&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;upper-year-project-mentorship&quot;&gt;7. Upper year project mentorship&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The IGEN council is searching for up to 10 3rd of 4th year students to help with the IGEN 230 class. Your role would be to help mentor a second year project group, providing advice for sourcing, industry night, and any other resources that they may need. This is very flexible and is an awesome way to meet more students in our department! If interested please email me at igenpresident@gmail.com. We already have a few people, but the more the merrier!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;sports-apparel&quot;&gt;8. Sports apparel&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IGEN will be doing athletic tops for the next IGEN apparel order. There are a few options (see attached document) so if you are interested please fill out the facebook poll (in the IGEN Group) and indicate which option(s) you would like and what color (black, red, white). After one week we will take all the feedback and determine which option we are going to order. The cost will be around $15&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;personal-branding-workshop&quot;&gt;9. Personal branding workshop&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This event will pair you with an experienced older student who can give you a hand with your resume, cover letter, interview skills, LinkedIn, you name it. The idea is to help you tailor your applications to best achieve the positions you want. This is a super valuable opportunity, and can push you towards success. Come on out this Wednesday, January 27th, from 5-7PM in the IGEN clubroom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/1695228674051828/&quot;&gt;Facebook Event&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;first-aid-course&quot;&gt;10. First Aid course&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So you may have seen a signup sheet in the IGEN clubroom last semester for an Emergency first aid course coming to certify IGEN students. We have set a date for this on February 27th from 9:00 to 5:00 on UBC campus (exact room to be determined) and will cost $85. If you are interested and would like to sign up or get more information, please send me an email at lance.cburnett@gmail.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The certification is Emergency First Aid with CPR/AED Level C.
Students outside of IGEN are welcome to join, however we would like to give IGEN students the opportunity to sign up first (there are limited seats) so please wait until Wednesday (January 27) before inviting them.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2016/01/25/Presidents-Update-January-25/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2016/01/25/Presidents-Update-January-25/</guid>
        
        
        <category>president-update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>President&#39;s Update for January 18 2016</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey everyone,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a very long update this week as there is a lot of stuff going on. Please read through as there are a number of excellent opportunities to take hold of, and places to get involved. Without further ado, here are your updates:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;e-week-signup&quot;&gt;1. E-Week Signup&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IGEN! E-Week is almost upon us! Two more weeks until the festivities commence and it is now time to open signup for events and activities. Please see the attached Google Drive folder link for detailed schedules, rules and the all important signup sheets to make sure we know you’re coming to the great events the EUS has planned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=16eIR1f07O3jBWWVbsDXIg6kPhgN6FmjIFXySrS3C2y8&quot;&gt;Sign up sheet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THESE WILL FILL UP - most of the sport/competition events have a limited number of entries from each department, so as soon as those quotas are met I will close registration for those sections. SIGN UP ASAP!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the social events, put your name down for the ones you’re interested in so that you can see which of your friends are interested in going! This year IGEN has a great opportunity to not only fight for the the title of E-Week champs, but also to put our best foot forward as the brightest up-and-coming program in the faculty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned for more updates and we can’t wait to see you during E-Week!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;pre-e-week-party&quot;&gt;2. Pre-E-Week Party&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Friday, January 29th (next week!) will be IGEN’s Pre-E-Week party! We’ll be getting getting into the E-Week spirit with tryouts for Boat Races and Foosball. Beer and snacks will be provided for the tryouts! The event will start at 4pm and take place in our clubroom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;genius-bowl&quot;&gt;3. Genius Bowl&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Genius Bowl is the EUS’ annual pub-style lecture hall trivia competition. Do you know enough to win the trophy? Prove it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tuesday January 19, 2016 (TOMORROW)
6:30pm-8:30pm
CHBE 102
Register your team at ubcengineers.ca/geniusbowl&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;blood-drive&quot;&gt;4. Blood Drive&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are you ready to give? It’s time for another EUS blood drive! We are adopting the Oak St. Clinic on January 27th &amp;amp; 28th.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By signing up and donating with us (or giving blood to research if you aren’t qualified to donate!), you can collect charity points and get yourself on your way to earning a Charity Patch for your Red. In addition, you can ALSO earn points for your Department in the Blood Cup! At the end of the year, the Department with the most points will win the coveted Blood Trophy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sign up using the form at ubcengineers.ca/blood and check out the Facebook event at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/1727498030819830/&quot;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have a group of four or more, please contact Cherise Louie directly at (778) 837-5097 to organize appointments as well as transportation. Larger groups will be able to control their own times so it may be more convenient for you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;faculty-cup&quot;&gt;5. Faculty Cup&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The insatiable rumors and word on the malls are true- Faculty Cup is back and bigger than ever! On January 29th, we’re rollin’ out the faculty colours and unleashing those friendly rivalries in UBC’s only faculty vs. faculty competition. Think you’ve got what it takes to be great this coming January? Faculty Cup will be here to put your faculty to the test. For more info and to register go to:
facultycup.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;upper-year-project-mentorship&quot;&gt;6. Upper year project mentorship&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The IGEN council is searching for up to 10 3rd of 4th year students to help with the IGEN 230 class. Your role would be to help mentor a second year project group, providing advice for sourcing, industry night, and any other resources that they may need. This is very flexible and is an awesome way to meet more students in our department! If interested please email me at igenpresident@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;career-fair&quot;&gt;7. Career Fair&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main EUS career fair of the year is coming up soon! Details here:
Feb 4 and 5. 10am to 3pm. Kaiser Atrium / KAIS 2020/2030.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ubcengineers.ca/services/professional/career-fair/&quot;&gt;Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Email careerfair@ubcengineers.ca / volunteer@ubcengineers.ca to get involved!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks so much for your attention through this long email.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2016/01/18/Presidents-Update-January-18/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2016/01/18/Presidents-Update-January-18/</guid>
        
        
        <category>president-update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>President&#39;s Update for January 11 2016</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Good afternoon everyone,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are your notices for this week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;igen-spaces&quot;&gt;1. IGEN spaces&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The IGEN areas, specifically the electrical shop and the computer lab, have been getting very cluttered. Please make sure to remove your tools and work after you finish and leave the area as you found it. This is a communal space we are very lucky to have, so please respect it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;igen-shop-supervision&quot;&gt;2. IGEN Shop supervision&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The IGEN shop will be creating a new schedule for the semester now that everyone’s classes have changed. New shop supervisors are welcome, note that shop supervisors are provided card access to the shop at all times. The position requires one or two hours of shop supervision each week. If you would like to become a shop supervisor for this semester please send an email to the shop manager, Lachlan, at lockiepeds1@gmail.com before Wednesday, January 13th.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;printer-paper&quot;&gt;3. Printer paper&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The printer has been running out of paper quite often. In response we have put extra in the shop locker, please ask the shop supervisor on duty for extra if the printer has run out. Also be sure to print multiple slides per page if printing class notes. We have large boxes of paper on order so hopefully this issue will be resolved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;iron-ring-ceremony&quot;&gt;4. Iron Ring Ceremony&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There will be MANDATORY info sessions ~1-2 weeks before the ceremony itself - dates are still being settled. You must attend the info session in order to attend the ceremony. There will be two info sessions, and we will assign each department to one session. Grads must attend the correct session.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Iron Ring ceremony will be on March 9th. Logistics coming soon, but last year doors opened ~1:30pm and it ran until 4pm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes: this is something you skip class for (both the info session and the ceremony). I will be contacting all professors in APSC and letting them know about the date as soon as possible. Most of the time, profs are pretty good about this - they understand that it is important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks everyone, and have a lovely week.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2016/01/11/Presidents-Update-January-11/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2016/01/11/Presidents-Update-January-11/</guid>
        
        
        <category>president-update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>President&#39;s Update for January 4 2016</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope you had a wonderful holiday break. This week the update will be short as we get geared back up for school.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;iron-ring-ceremony&quot;&gt;1. Iron Ring Ceremony&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There will be MANDATORY info sessions ~1-2 weeks before the ceremony itself - dates are still being settled. You must attend the info session in order to attend the ceremony. There will be two info sessions, and we will assign each department to one session. Grads must attend the correct session.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Iron Ring ceremony will be on March 9th. Logistics coming soon, but last year doors opened ~1:30pm and it ran until 4pm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes: this is something you skip class for (both the info session and the ceremony). I will be contacting all professors in APSC and letting them know about the date as soon as possible. Most of the time, profs are pretty good about this - they understand that it is important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;e-week-teams&quot;&gt;2. E-Week teams&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The e-week teams have been made and emails sent out from the various team leaders. If you would still like to be involved with the teams please email Jesse, our e-week coordinator, at jmacht@shaw.ca&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks everyone, and welcome back!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2016/01/04/Presidents-Update-January-04/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2016/01/04/Presidents-Update-January-04/</guid>
        
        
        <category>president-update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>President&#39;s Update for November 30 2015</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are your updates for the last week of school! Stay strong, you’re almost there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;e-week-teams&quot;&gt;1. E-Week Teams&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jesse, our E-Week rep, has posted some preliminary teams on the IGEN Facebook group. The poll is the top pinned post. Please sign up for these groups, as they are an awesome way to use your engineering skills in a fun competition and represent your department!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/groups/ubcigen/?fref=ts&quot;&gt;Facebook Event&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;first-aid-courses&quot;&gt;2. First Aid courses&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IGEN is considering bringing in an instructor to teach emergency first aid on Saturday or Sunday in the second week of January. We will hold sessions on both days if there is enough interest. The session is 8 hours and will cost $85. There will be sign up sheets in the clubroom for both days. Please sign up on one of the days to express your interest. A minimum of 15 people is required per session, so if we have less than 15 on a day, then we may combine groups and have one session.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks everyone, and enjoy the week!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2015/11/30/Presidents-Update-November-30/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2015/11/30/Presidents-Update-November-30/</guid>
        
        
        <category>president-update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>President&#39;s Update for November 23 2015</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Good afternoon,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apologies for the late email today. Here are the weekly updates:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;krispy-kreme-fundraiser&quot;&gt;1. Krispy Kreme Fundraiser&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Donuts are being sold this week until Thursday in the Kaiser Atrium! 
We will be setting up a booth in the Kaiser Atrium from November 23  - 26 (11 am - 2 pm everyday) and will be selling Krispy Kreme donuts for cheap:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$10/dozen, $1/single donut&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Come out and support our department buy buying some delicious treats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;igen-jackets&quot;&gt;2. IGEN Jackets&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you to all who signed up to purchase a jacket. Due to the size of our order they will not be finished until January. Thus, hold tight for payment options and information, as well as expected pickup dates. Thanks for your patience!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;eus-football-tournament&quot;&gt;3. EUS Football Tournament&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IGEN had to two teams playing this past Sunday in the EUS Flag Football event. Both teams played very well and represented the department with pride. Big shout out to Tanya Bennet, our sports rep for her organization and Alex Hutchinson, EUS VP Student Life for making the whole tournament a reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;igen-general-meeting&quot;&gt;4. IGEN General Meeting&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you to all who came to the General Meeting last friday. Some excellent discussion took place surround e-week and the IGEN Council’s performance up to this point. As we did not have time to complete our goals discussing future events and initiatives you can expect some polls to appear in the near future on the IGEN facebook pages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks everyone, and have a fantastic week. This week our photo shows some alternative but no less important applications of engineering knowledge; letting this little cutie walk again!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2015/11/23/Presidents-Update-November-23/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2015/11/23/Presidents-Update-November-23/</guid>
        
        
        <category>president-update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
