<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UBC Integrated Engineers</title>
    <description>Student run website of the UBC Integrated Engineers. This site is a resource for current students, prospective students, alumni and industry members.
</description>
    <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://integratedengineers.ca/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 10:03:21 -0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 10:03:21 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.0.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>President&#39;s Update for January 18 2016</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey everyone,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a very long update this week as there is a lot of stuff going on. Please read through as there are a number of excellent opportunities to take hold of, and places to get involved. Without further ado, here are your updates:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;e-week-signup&quot;&gt;1. E-Week Signup&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IGEN! E-Week is almost upon us! Two more weeks until the festivities commence and it is now time to open signup for events and activities. Please see the attached Google Drive folder link for detailed schedules, rules and the all important signup sheets to make sure we know you’re coming to the great events the EUS has planned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=16eIR1f07O3jBWWVbsDXIg6kPhgN6FmjIFXySrS3C2y8&quot;&gt;Sign up sheet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THESE WILL FILL UP - most of the sport/competition events have a limited number of entries from each department, so as soon as those quotas are met I will close registration for those sections. SIGN UP ASAP!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the social events, put your name down for the ones you’re interested in so that you can see which of your friends are interested in going! This year IGEN has a great opportunity to not only fight for the the title of E-Week champs, but also to put our best foot forward as the brightest up-and-coming program in the faculty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned for more updates and we can’t wait to see you during E-Week!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;pre-e-week-party&quot;&gt;2. Pre-E-Week Party&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Friday, January 29th (next week!) will be IGEN’s Pre-E-Week party! We’ll be getting getting into the E-Week spirit with tryouts for Boat Races and Foosball. Beer and snacks will be provided for the tryouts! The event will start at 4pm and take place in our clubroom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;genius-bowl&quot;&gt;3. Genius Bowl&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Genius Bowl is the EUS’ annual pub-style lecture hall trivia competition. Do you know enough to win the trophy? Prove it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tuesday January 19, 2016 (TOMORROW)
6:30pm-8:30pm
CHBE 102
Register your team at ubcengineers.ca/geniusbowl&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;blood-drive&quot;&gt;4. Blood Drive&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are you ready to give? It’s time for another EUS blood drive! We are adopting the Oak St. Clinic on January 27th &amp;amp; 28th.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By signing up and donating with us (or giving blood to research if you aren’t qualified to donate!), you can collect charity points and get yourself on your way to earning a Charity Patch for your Red. In addition, you can ALSO earn points for your Department in the Blood Cup! At the end of the year, the Department with the most points will win the coveted Blood Trophy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sign up using the form at ubcengineers.ca/blood and check out the Facebook event at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/1727498030819830/&quot;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have a group of four or more, please contact Cherise Louie directly at (778) 837-5097 to organize appointments as well as transportation. Larger groups will be able to control their own times so it may be more convenient for you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;faculty-cup&quot;&gt;5. Faculty Cup&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The insatiable rumors and word on the malls are true- Faculty Cup is back and bigger than ever! On January 29th, we’re rollin’ out the faculty colours and unleashing those friendly rivalries in UBC’s only faculty vs. faculty competition. Think you’ve got what it takes to be great this coming January? Faculty Cup will be here to put your faculty to the test. For more info and to register go to:
facultycup.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;upper-year-project-mentorship&quot;&gt;6. Upper year project mentorship&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The IGEN council is searching for up to 10 3rd of 4th year students to help with the IGEN 230 class. Your role would be to help mentor a second year project group, providing advice for sourcing, industry night, and any other resources that they may need. This is very flexible and is an awesome way to meet more students in our department! If interested please email me at igenpresident@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;career-fair&quot;&gt;7. Career Fair&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main EUS career fair of the year is coming up soon! Details here:
Feb 4 and 5. 10am to 3pm. Kaiser Atrium / KAIS 2020/2030.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ubcengineers.ca/services/professional/career-fair/&quot;&gt;Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Email careerfair@ubcengineers.ca / volunteer@ubcengineers.ca to get involved!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks so much for your attention through this long email.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2016/01/18/Presidents-Update-January-18/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2016/01/18/Presidents-Update-January-18/</guid>
        
        
        <category>president-update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>President&#39;s Update for January 11 2016</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Good afternoon everyone,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are your notices for this week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;igen-spaces&quot;&gt;1. IGEN spaces&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The IGEN areas, specifically the electrical shop and the computer lab, have been getting very cluttered. Please make sure to remove your tools and work after you finish and leave the area as you found it. This is a communal space we are very lucky to have, so please respect it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;igen-shop-supervision&quot;&gt;2. IGEN Shop supervision&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The IGEN shop will be creating a new schedule for the semester now that everyone’s classes have changed. New shop supervisors are welcome, note that shop supervisors are provided card access to the shop at all times. The position requires one or two hours of shop supervision each week. If you would like to become a shop supervisor for this semester please send an email to the shop manager, Lachlan, at lockiepeds1@gmail.com before Wednesday, January 13th.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;printer-paper&quot;&gt;3. Printer paper&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The printer has been running out of paper quite often. In response we have put extra in the shop locker, please ask the shop supervisor on duty for extra if the printer has run out. Also be sure to print multiple slides per page if printing class notes. We have large boxes of paper on order so hopefully this issue will be resolved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;iron-ring-ceremony&quot;&gt;4. Iron Ring Ceremony&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There will be MANDATORY info sessions ~1-2 weeks before the ceremony itself - dates are still being settled. You must attend the info session in order to attend the ceremony. There will be two info sessions, and we will assign each department to one session. Grads must attend the correct session.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Iron Ring ceremony will be on March 9th. Logistics coming soon, but last year doors opened ~1:30pm and it ran until 4pm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes: this is something you skip class for (both the info session and the ceremony). I will be contacting all professors in APSC and letting them know about the date as soon as possible. Most of the time, profs are pretty good about this - they understand that it is important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks everyone, and have a lovely week.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2016/01/11/Presidents-Update-January-11/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2016/01/11/Presidents-Update-January-11/</guid>
        
        
        <category>president-update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>President&#39;s Update for January 4 2016</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope you had a wonderful holiday break. This week the update will be short as we get geared back up for school.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;iron-ring-ceremony&quot;&gt;1. Iron Ring Ceremony&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There will be MANDATORY info sessions ~1-2 weeks before the ceremony itself - dates are still being settled. You must attend the info session in order to attend the ceremony. There will be two info sessions, and we will assign each department to one session. Grads must attend the correct session.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Iron Ring ceremony will be on March 9th. Logistics coming soon, but last year doors opened ~1:30pm and it ran until 4pm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes: this is something you skip class for (both the info session and the ceremony). I will be contacting all professors in APSC and letting them know about the date as soon as possible. Most of the time, profs are pretty good about this - they understand that it is important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;e-week-teams&quot;&gt;2. E-Week teams&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The e-week teams have been made and emails sent out from the various team leaders. If you would still like to be involved with the teams please email Jesse, our e-week coordinator, at jmacht@shaw.ca&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks everyone, and welcome back!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2016/01/04/Presidents-Update-January-04/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2016/01/04/Presidents-Update-January-04/</guid>
        
        
        <category>president-update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>President&#39;s Update for November 30 2015</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are your updates for the last week of school! Stay strong, you’re almost there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;e-week-teams&quot;&gt;1. E-Week Teams&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jesse, our E-Week rep, has posted some preliminary teams on the IGEN Facebook group. The poll is the top pinned post. Please sign up for these groups, as they are an awesome way to use your engineering skills in a fun competition and represent your department!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/groups/ubcigen/?fref=ts&quot;&gt;Facebook Event&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;first-aid-courses&quot;&gt;2. First Aid courses&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IGEN is considering bringing in an instructor to teach emergency first aid on Saturday or Sunday in the second week of January. We will hold sessions on both days if there is enough interest. The session is 8 hours and will cost $85. There will be sign up sheets in the clubroom for both days. Please sign up on one of the days to express your interest. A minimum of 15 people is required per session, so if we have less than 15 on a day, then we may combine groups and have one session.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks everyone, and enjoy the week!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2015/11/30/Presidents-Update-November-30/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2015/11/30/Presidents-Update-November-30/</guid>
        
        
        <category>president-update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>President&#39;s Update for November 23 2015</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Good afternoon,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apologies for the late email today. Here are the weekly updates:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;krispy-kreme-fundraiser&quot;&gt;1. Krispy Kreme Fundraiser&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Donuts are being sold this week until Thursday in the Kaiser Atrium! 
We will be setting up a booth in the Kaiser Atrium from November 23  - 26 (11 am - 2 pm everyday) and will be selling Krispy Kreme donuts for cheap:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$10/dozen, $1/single donut&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Come out and support our department buy buying some delicious treats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;igen-jackets&quot;&gt;2. IGEN Jackets&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you to all who signed up to purchase a jacket. Due to the size of our order they will not be finished until January. Thus, hold tight for payment options and information, as well as expected pickup dates. Thanks for your patience!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;eus-football-tournament&quot;&gt;3. EUS Football Tournament&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IGEN had to two teams playing this past Sunday in the EUS Flag Football event. Both teams played very well and represented the department with pride. Big shout out to Tanya Bennet, our sports rep for her organization and Alex Hutchinson, EUS VP Student Life for making the whole tournament a reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;igen-general-meeting&quot;&gt;4. IGEN General Meeting&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you to all who came to the General Meeting last friday. Some excellent discussion took place surround e-week and the IGEN Council’s performance up to this point. As we did not have time to complete our goals discussing future events and initiatives you can expect some polls to appear in the near future on the IGEN facebook pages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks everyone, and have a fantastic week. This week our photo shows some alternative but no less important applications of engineering knowledge; letting this little cutie walk again!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2015/11/23/Presidents-Update-November-23/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2015/11/23/Presidents-Update-November-23/</guid>
        
        
        <category>president-update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>President&#39;s Update for November 16 2015</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some very important updates below, so please read through today!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;igen-general-meeting&quot;&gt;1. IGEN General Meeting&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Integrated Engineering Council will be hosting a General Meeting for all students on Friday, November 20th, from 12:00 - 2:00 PM in CEME 1202. The goals of this meeting are to gain feedback regarding council activities up to this point, and have students discuss plans for next semester. Also discussed will be classes and curriculum, e-week consultation done in conjunction with the EUS, and assorted other IGEN related topics. Refreshments will be provided. Come and have a say in how your program functions!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;igen-jackets&quot;&gt;2. IGEN jackets&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IGEN jackets are available to order! Here are the details:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Price: $110-$120 depending on how many we sell, so get your friends out!
Sizing: XS to XL, men’s and women’s
Colour: Slate for Men, Platinum or Black for Women&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To try on sizing we have all of the sizes available in the IGEN clubroom until Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please fill out the following survey to order your jacket! We will detail payment options as soon as we have a final number on the orders. Please note orders are due by Wednesday Nov 18th at 12 noon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://survey.ubc.ca/s/igen-jacket-signup/&quot;&gt;IGEN Jacket Order Form&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;krispy-kreme-fundraiser&quot;&gt;3. Krispy Kreme fundraiser&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Krispy Kreme Fundraiser - Help Wanted!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IGEN is growing in numbers each year and we need money to help cover costs for our shop supplies, clubroom, student affairs, and industry outreach. We will be setting up a booth in the Kaiser Atrium from November 23  - 26 (11 am - 2 pm everyday) and will be selling Krispy Kreme donuts for cheap:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$10/dozen, $1/single donut&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Help booth, sell donuts and spread the word about IGEN! If you got 30mins to spare, or even more, help would be greatly appreciated! Sign up sheet will be posted on the bulletin in the clubroom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Invite your friends to the facebook event (and check our new IGEN logo!):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/1046686905381749/&quot;&gt;Facebook Event&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For questions, email Jael at igentreasurer@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you all, and we’ll see you this Friday at the General Meeting!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2015/11/16/Presidents-Update-November-16/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2015/11/16/Presidents-Update-November-16/</guid>
        
        
        <category>president-update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Meet an IGENeer - Jesse Macht</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; src=&quot;https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/12440671/10349967/4125caa2-6cf6-11e5-950e-95635269af20.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hello, my name is Jesse Macht and I am in my fourth year of Integrated Engineering. I am interested in fluid dynamics and controls engineering, so I have taken courses related to these interests through the Mechanical and Electrical departments, respectively. I have worked with design project teams and a local start up on the development of UAV technology for remote sensing applications in industry. I have also been involved in academic research into the lightweight alloys used for modern automotive and energy applications, both at UBC and McMaster University in Hamilton, Ontario.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Besides the academic and industry work I am involved in, I am very invested in engaging Integrating Engineering students on the social side of their degree experience. This year I am the E-Week representative for the Integrated Engineering Council and I am working with both the EUS and the Council to reimagine how we engage socially through E-Week events and activities. Please do not hesitate to contact me regarding E-Week, any of my academic or industry work, or about the IGEN degree in general. I would love to speak with you!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/meet-an-igeneer/2015/11/16/Meet-an-IGENeer-Jesse-Macht/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/meet-an-igeneer/2015/11/16/Meet-an-IGENeer-Jesse-Macht/</guid>
        
        
        <category>meet-an-IGENeer</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>President&#39;s Update for November 9 2015</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Good morning,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are a couple important announcements for the coming week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;krispy-kreme-fundraiser&quot;&gt;1. Krispy Kreme Fundraiser&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Krispy Kreme Fundraiser - Help Wanted!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IGEN is growing in numbers each year and we need money to help cover costs for our shop supplies, clubroom, student affairs, and industry outreach. We will be setting up a booth in the Kaiser Atrium from November 23  - 26 (11 am - 2 pm everyday) and will be selling Krispy Kreme donuts for cheap:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$10/dozen, $1/single donut&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Help booth, sell donuts and spread the word about IGEN! If you got 30mins to spare, or even more, help would be greatly appreciated! Sign up sheet will be posted on the bulletin in the clubroom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Invite your friends to the facebook event (and check our new IGEN logo!):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/1046686905381749/&quot;&gt;Facebook Event&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For questions, email Jael at igentreasurer@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;lunch-around-the-world&quot;&gt;2. Lunch Around the World&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The EUS on November 20th is hosting an event celebrating multiculturalism and food, two things we can all get behind! If someone wants to create an IGEN team and cook some awesome food, signup and details can be found below. Please note the deadline is November 11th for signup!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/1515636585425788/&quot;&gt;Facebook Event&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ubcengineers.ca/events/social/lunch-around-the-world/&quot;&gt;EUS Website and Signup&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you all for your attention, and have a great week!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2015/11/09/Presidents-Update-November-09/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2015/11/09/Presidents-Update-November-09/</guid>
        
        
        <category>president-update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>President&#39;s Update for November 2 2015</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Good morning,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are a few updates for you all:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;academic-consulatation&quot;&gt;1. Academic Consulatation&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This evening all of the year reps and our VP Academic will be representing the department at the EUS Grand Council. There we will be providing feedback regarding our courses and areas for improvement. If you have any constructive feedback regarding our courses and changes you would like to see, please let any of the mentioned people above know, comment on the related Facebook posts, or reply to this email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;grad&quot;&gt;2. Grad&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have not yet had your ring sized or paid you gown deposit, please contact Cobi immediately. Also if you did not get your grad photos taken during the set aside blocks you must call Evangelos Photography and arrange your own appointment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;bulletin-board&quot;&gt;3. Bulletin Board&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to Hailey, we have a new bulletin board in the clubroom! The top portion is to be used by IGEN Council for updates, whereas the bottom portion is or you, our students, to make announcements to the department at large. Any inappropriate language or content  will be removed without notice, and after an event has passed the poster will be removed unless otherwise notified.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2015/11/02/Presidents-Update-November-02/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2015/11/02/Presidents-Update-November-02/</guid>
        
        
        <category>president-update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IGEN CEO Speaker Series: Darby Kreitz</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; src=&quot;/images/DarbyKreitz1.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Darby Kreitz addressing IGEN students&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IGEN 340 hosted renowned entrepreneur Darby Kreitz for a CEO Speaker Series talk.
The event took place in Frank Forward 303.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Darby Kreitz is the CEO of Allnorth Consultants Ltd, a company with just 4 people in 1995 to over 550 people today. Kreitz gave a talk on his background, his leadership style and the importance of choosing a good team to work with. A highlight from his talk was how he chooses “&lt;strong&gt;Attitude over Aptitude&lt;/strong&gt;”: Insisting that while it is important to have good technically minded people on the team, it is even more important that people can fit well together and work as a unit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; src=&quot;/images/DarbyKreitz2.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Darby Kreitz addressing IGEN students&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He proposes his famous “&lt;strong&gt;four hour pickup truck test&lt;/strong&gt;” as a way to hire people, saying that when you want someone on the team, think about whether you can enjoy a 4 hour long pickup truck ride with them. If the answer is no, you probably don’t want to work with them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IGEN is grateful to Mr Darby Kreitz for presenting today and Mr Mark Dance, IGEN 340 instructor, for facilitating the CEO Speakers Series.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; src=&quot;/images/DarbyKreitz3.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Darby Kreitz addressing IGEN students&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/ceo-speaker-series/2015/10/29/IGEN-CEO-Speaker_Series-Darby-Kreitz/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/ceo-speaker-series/2015/10/29/IGEN-CEO-Speaker_Series-Darby-Kreitz/</guid>
        
        
        <category>CEO-Speaker-Series</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
