<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UBC Integrated Engineers</title>
    <description>Student run website of the UBC Integrated Engineers. This site is a resource for current students, prospective students, alumni and industry members.
</description>
    <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://integratedengineers.ca/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 10:10:11 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 10:10:11 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>President&#39;s Update for March 14 2016</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are a lot of updates this week as it is a busy time at IGEN HQ. Please take the time to review everything as there is some critical information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;igen-council-elections&quot;&gt;1. IGEN Council Elections&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another year gone, and it’s time for another election! We will be accepting nominations for the various council roles starting today! In the clubroom there is a stack of nomination forms and a box to deposit them in. The positions up for election are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;President&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Vice President External&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Vice President Internal&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Vice President Academic&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Vice President Student Life&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Vice President Communications&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Treasurer&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Chief Shop Supervisor&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sports Representative&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Graduation Representative&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Information about each one’s roles can be found in the attached document. Also the person currently occupying the position is named, should you have any questions. The Facebook event where you can keep track of everything is at the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/1678817432399135/&quot;&gt;Facebook Event&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;igen-project-showcase---project-information&quot;&gt;2. IGEN Project Showcase - Project Information&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The form below MUST be filled out by one member of each project team in IGEN 230, 330, and 430. Please complete this form ASAP as this information is required for the event brochure. THIS IS DIFFERENT FROM THE OTHER FORM YOU FILLED OUT, YOU MUST DO IT AGAIN.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1HIMtYUFM8iEfKeHA7aFWfyRdKN4dwpn8TbX80NB5yvA/viewform&quot;&gt;Google Form&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;eus-elections&quot;&gt;3. EUS elections&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your EUS Elections have officially begun! We hope you are ready for two weeks of excitement, as our 2016-2017 Executive will be voted in BY YOU. Get informed by checking out all of your candidates at: Blog Link. As well, you can check out the Official EUS Debates at 5PM on Tuesday and Wednesday in the ESC! There will be FREE PIZZA for all in attendance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For your ALL ACCESS pass to the EUS Elections, check out our official facebook event at: Facebook Event&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;eus-futsal-tournament&quot;&gt;4. EUS Futsal Tournament&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The EUS is hosting its annual futsal tournament in the SRC on March 31st. We always have a lot of interest for this event so we will be hosting tryouts for the IGEN team. The tryouts will be Wednesday, March 16th, at the drop-in futsal at the SRC. Make sure to come early to make sure you get in! WE NEED GIRLS AND BOYS. More details about the tournament can be found in the following Facebook group.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/1674926169428213/&quot;&gt;Facebook Event&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;igen-space-cleanup&quot;&gt;5. IGEN Space cleanup&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This year the first year’s clubroom crawl will be taking place the day after Industry Night. This means that we need our space to be sparkling clean before Industry Night begins. As part of your requirements before setting up for Industry Night we will need the IGEN Clubroom, shop, and electrical room to be spotless. This means everyone must do their part to help clean up everything. You WILL NOT BE ALLOWED TO SET UP UNTIL EVERYTHING IS CLEAN. More details will be released closer to the event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;environmental-engineering-clothing-exchange&quot;&gt;6. Environmental Engineering clothing exchange&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our neighbours the Environmental Engineers are hosting a clothing exchange! Please contact &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#101;&amp;#110;&amp;#118;&amp;#101;&amp;#117;&amp;#098;&amp;#099;&amp;#064;&amp;#103;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;&quot;&gt;&amp;#101;&amp;#110;&amp;#118;&amp;#101;&amp;#117;&amp;#098;&amp;#099;&amp;#064;&amp;#103;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for your attention, and have a wonderful week!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2016/03/14/Presidents-Update-March-14/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2016/03/14/Presidents-Update-March-14/</guid>
        
        
        <category>president-update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IGEN Council Roles Explained</title>
        <description>&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;President&lt;/strong&gt; – Current: Gabriel Lessard-Kragen&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Preside over meetings of the Club, the Council, and the
Executive Council&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Represent the Club on the EUS Board of Directors or appoint a
representative to the position&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Enforce due observance of the Constitution and Policy Manual&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Shall represent only the majority opinion of the Council when
acting on behalf of the Club&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Shall be the liaison between the Council and other EUS Clubs&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Supervise and direct the duties of the Executive and
Representative Councils, and be familiar with the entire
contents of the Policy Manual&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Represent the Club to the Faculty of Applied Science, the EUS,
to the University, the AMS and any other recognized club or
organization&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Rectify any violations of the Constitution or Policy Manual as
soon as possible, and report such violations to the council in a
timely manner&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Must organize the transition between incoming and outgoing
Councils&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Obtain and make available to the Club information concerning all
Engineering organizations of interest to the students&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Send notice of all forthcoming events to the Faculty&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Oversee the vision of the Club and the department in conjunction
with Faculty&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;!-- --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vice President External&lt;/strong&gt; – Currently: Mathieu Haiart &amp;amp; Kiel Olver&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Assume the duties of the President of the Club in their absence&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Ensure club representation on Faculty and University committees
as necessary&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Be the liaison between the Club, other Engineering Student
Societies, and public affairs&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Be responsible for the submission of article to technical
journals as required&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Be responsible for the submission of articles to the EUS
publications as required&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Be responsible for organizing the IGEN Project Showcase as
required&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Be responsible for organizing and Alumni related events&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;!-- --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vice President Internal&lt;/strong&gt; – Currently: Hailey Grotkowski&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Assume the duties of the President of the Club in the absence of
both the President and the Vice-President External&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Co-ordinate all affairs related to, and maintain all, physical
academic resources of the Club&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Co-ordinate all activities related to the general well-being of
IGEN students, both on campus and in the community&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Co-ordinate the food sales through the Club as a service to
members&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Co-ordinate the activities of the Representative Council with
the Fourth Year Representative&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Be responsible for all internal correspondence of the Club&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Be responsible for the neatness of the notice boards with the
clubhouse&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;!-- --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vice President Academic&lt;/strong&gt; – Currently: Achintya Verma&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Bi-monthly meetings with IGEN course instructors and submit a
report to IGEN program director&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Set-up academic discussions every term with IGEN program
director&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Oversee the academic services offered by the Society&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Organize and maintain course material documents with help of
year reps&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Communicating with professors to move midterms and assignments
during E-Week&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Represent IGEN student interests to the EUS on academic matters&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;!-- --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vice President Student Life&lt;/strong&gt; – Currently: Will Stratton&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Oversee the events co-ordinated by the club&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Promote the club to both IGEN club members and the external
community&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Actively organize regular social events for IGEN club members&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Organize IGEN club clothing/apparel purchasing and management&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Work closely with the E-Week co-ordinator&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Responsible for advertising events hosted by IGEN Club&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;!-- --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vice President Communications&lt;/strong&gt; – Currently: Darshan Soni&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Build, maintain, and update the IGEN website as required by the
Council&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Administer the IGEN Google Apps accounts and domain name&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Be responsible for regular updates to IGEN social media accounts&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Maintain the communications team and their output of content&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Organize photography for all IGEN events and maintain the
storage of such pictures&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;!-- --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Treasurer&lt;/strong&gt; – Currently: Jael Lumba&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Submit a budget for approval by Council before the end of the
Spring term&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Be responsible for the distribution of club funds in accordance
with the budget&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Submit all budgets and balance sheets as required to the Club on
monthly basis&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Obtain estimates of all proposed expenditures&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Arrange club purchases and the payment of club debts&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Supervise the sale and distribution of tickets for club
functions&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Work in conjunction with the incoming Treasurer in preparing the
next year’s budget&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Brief the incoming Treasurer on the current state of all Club
financial affairs before they take office in March&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Be the sole signing officer of the Club&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Ensure only expenditures approved by the council at a weekly
meeting are paid from Club funds&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;!-- --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chief Shop Supervisor&lt;/strong&gt; – Currently: Lachlan Pedersen&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Restocking of hardware as well as sufficient tool upgrades&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Safety-orientation and training of selected shop supervisors
each term&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Selection and scheduling of shop supervisors&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Recommendation and training of future chief shop supervisor&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Maintenance of shop space&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;!-- --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Graduation Representative&lt;/strong&gt; – Currently: Cobi Yu&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Co-ordinate with the appropriate EUS Representative on all
activities concerned with the Iron Ring Ceremony, Convocation
Ceremony, Class Act committee and the Grad Class Council&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Be responsible for graduation class photos&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Be responsible for organizing the Grad Trip, if applicable&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Not hold any future Executive Council positions, in order to
maintain the integrity of this position&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;!-- --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sports Representative&lt;/strong&gt; – Currently: Tanya Bennet&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Co-ordinate the formation and administration of all IGEN
composed sports teams&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Publicize upcoming sporting events and recruit IGEN members
where necessary&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Work with the Treasurer and EUS VP Finance to coordinate the
funding and reimbursement of IGEN sports related expenses, where
applicable&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/igen-council/2016/03/08/IGEN-Council-Roles/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/igen-council/2016/03/08/IGEN-Council-Roles/</guid>
        
        
        <category>IGEN-Council</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>President&#39;s Update for March 07 2016</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey y’all,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;igen-council-elections&quot;&gt;1. IGEN Council Elections&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another year gone, and it’s time for another election! We will be accepting nominations for the various council roles starting Monday, March 14th. More information will be released in the following week, but the positions up for election are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;President&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Vice President External&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Vice President Internal&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Vice President Academic&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Vice President Student Life&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Vice President Commincations&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Treasurer&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Chief Shop Supervisor&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sports Representative&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Graduation Representative&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Information about each one’s roles can be found in the attached document (to be updated shortly). Also the person currently occupying the position is named, should you have any questions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;kiewit-seminar-series&quot;&gt;2. Kiewit Seminar Series&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second installment of the IGEN Seminar Series is here, and it is being lead by Jason Block Of Kiewit. This is a great opportunity to learn about Kiewit, and positions available to both graduating students and students interested in summer positions. There will be a short 40 minute presentation, 10 minutes of questions and ample time for networking. Pizza and pop will be provided! Please follow the link below to find out more about the event:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/196759737355264/&quot;&gt;Facebook Event&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;eus-futsal-tournament&quot;&gt;3. EUS Futsal Tournament&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The EUS is hosting its annual futsal tournament in the SRC on March 31st. We always have a lot of interest for this event so we will be hosting tryouts for the IGEN team. The tryouts will be next Wednesday, March 16th, at the drop-in futsal at the SRC. Make sure to come early to make sure you get in! WE NEED GIRLS AND BOYS. More details about the tournament can be found in the following Facebook group.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/467119863492938/&quot;&gt;Facebook Event&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;iron-ring-reminder&quot;&gt;4. Iron Ring Reminder&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just a friendly reminder that the Iron Ring ceremony is this Wednesday, March 9th, at the Queen Elizabeth Theatre. Plan to be there by 12:45 PM to sign in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;igen-space-cleanup&quot;&gt;5. IGEN Space cleanup&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This year the first year’s clubroom crawl will be taking place the day after Industry Night. This means that we need our space to be sparkling clean before Industry Night begins. As part of your requirements before setting up for Industry Night we will need the IGEN Clubroom, shop, and electrical room to be spotless. This means everyone must do their part to help clean up everything. You WILL NOT BE ALLOWED TO SET UP UNTIL EVERYTHING IS CLEAN. More details will be released closer to the event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jackets&quot;&gt;6. Jackets&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The jackets have been ordered and are being made right now. Again, apologies for the delay.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2016/03/07/Presidents-Update-March-07/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2016/03/07/Presidents-Update-March-07/</guid>
        
        
        <category>president-update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>President&#39;s Update for February 29 2016</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are your updates. Apologies for the delay, some details for the jackets below were being ironed out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;igen-jackets&quot;&gt;1. IGEN Jackets&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know this has been a long and disappointing process, and trust me when I say no one is more frustrated with the delays on our jackets than I. I have moved distributors as the one we had an agreement with failed to hold up their side of the bargain. We are switching to a split of the Marmot and North Face Venture jacket. The price will now be the same for both, the sizing is the same, and the colour for the North Face will be Mid Grey Heather, which is the closest to the Marmot. We will be randomizing who gets which ones, and then if you want to trade with someone you are free to do so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would like to change your order please feel free to reply, otherwise we will keep your order from earlier and carry it over. Hopefully we can have these by Industry Night!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;kiewit-seminar&quot;&gt;2. Kiewit Seminar&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second installment of the IGEN Seminar Series is here, and it is being lead by Jason Block Of Kiewit. This is a great opportunity to learn about Kiewit, and positions available to both graduating students and students interested in summer positions. There will be a short 40 minute presentation, 10 minutes of questions and ample time for networking. Pizza and pop will be provided! Please follow the link below to find out more about the event:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/196759737355264/&quot;&gt;Facebook Event&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;igen-space-cleanup&quot;&gt;3. IGEN Space cleanup&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This year the first year’s clubroom crawl will be taking place the day after Industry Night. This means that we need our space to be sparkling clean before Industry Night begins. As part of your requirements before setting up for Industry Night we will need the IGEN Clubroom, shop, and electrical room to be spotless. This means everyone must do their part to help clean up everything. You WILL NOT BE ALLOWED TO SET UP UNTIL EVERYTHING IS CLEAN. More details will be released closer to the event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;iron-ring-after-party&quot;&gt;4. Iron Ring After Party&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The EUS is hosting an after party for the Iron Ring Ceremony on March 9th! The details can be found in the following facebook event:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/1689874447922300/&quot;&gt;Facebook Event&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for your attention, there’s only a month left of school!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Feb 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2016/02/29/Presidents-Update-February-29/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2016/02/29/Presidents-Update-February-29/</guid>
        
        
        <category>president-update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pitted Power Motor</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We are constructing an attachable surfboard motor. This will help new surfers battle currents and large waves. It will also be useful to those with disabilities, surf instructors, or those who find paddling tiring.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Team Members&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;David Keller&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Denny Lee&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Geneva Gordon&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Aaron Kopelow&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Shiv Mittal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/igen-project/2016/02/23/Pitted-Power-Motor/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/igen-project/2016/02/23/Pitted-Power-Motor/</guid>
        
        
        <category>IGEN-Project</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Smart Bathtub</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Smart Bathtub project is designed to enhance the bathing experience of people by providing remote access to bathtub using a cell phone or a tablet to control automatic-fill, temperature adjustments and jet settings. Sponsoring company: Valley Acrylic&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Team Members&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Aahil Shaikh&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Faheem Naser&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bana Batshon&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ata Basaran&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tan Hatipoglu&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tom Pauw&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tony Rainaldi&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Saif Al-Sulaiman&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/igen-project/2016/02/22/Smart-Bathtub/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/igen-project/2016/02/22/Smart-Bathtub/</guid>
        
        
        <category>IGEN-Project</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>President&#39;s Update for February 22 2016</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Good afternoon everyone,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope you all had a wonderful reading break and are feeling refreshed and ready to tackle the end of the school year! For those graduating, you’re almost there! This week we have some very important things that MUST be filled out in the next week, so please read carefully. Without further ado, here are the updates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;industry-night-student-listing---very-important&quot;&gt;1. Industry Night Student Listing - very important&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As with last year, we are preparing a list of all of our students and their year of study to put in a pamphlet for Industry Night. The idea is that this list will help potential employers see who is in the program and will allow sponsors a platform to present themselves to the student body. WE NEED EVERYONE’S FULL LEGAL NAME AND YEAR OF STUDY. If you do not want to be in the brochure, please email me with a reason. Your year of study should correspond to the project course you are enrolled in, i.e. the max is 4th. You do not want to be the one person not in the brochure when a recruiter takes it home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1fF86FzJGpYc1GK7ZzXni9lTuIbOzogWHm2FeK-BFfrY/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Google Sheet to Fill&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;igen-industry-night---invite-list---very-important&quot;&gt;2. IGEN Industry Night - Invite List - very important&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The IGEN Project Showcase will be held on April 6th, in the West Atrium of the Life Science Centre. The purpose of this event is to showcase your year long projects, and the IGEN program to professors, parents, and members of Industry. If would like to invite any members of industry, professors or your parents please follow the link below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1Fkmx8XejUMCXYncjDd-y5PuJqL6lJNO34NexxZtli3Q/viewform&quot;&gt;Google Form&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;igen-industry-night---project-information&quot;&gt;3. IGEN Industry Night - Project Information&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Darshan, our wonderful webmaster, is populating the website with all of the information about your projects. This information will also be put in the brochure distributed at Industry Night. EVERY PROJECT LEADER MUST FILL OUT THIS FORM. YOU CAN’T PRESENT AT INDUSTRY NIGHT WITHOUT DOING SO.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://survey.ubc.ca/s/igen-project-showcase/&quot;&gt;Survey Form&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;iron-ring-information-session&quot;&gt;4. Iron Ring information session&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grads: don’t forget to attend the MANDATORY Iron Ring Info Session on Thursday February 25th in the Norm Theatre!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You must attend this info session if you wish to receive your Iron Ring.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1:30-2:30pm Session: &lt;strong&gt;MINE, GEO, ELEC, IGEN, MECH&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2016/02/22/Presidents-Update-February-22/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/president-update/2016/02/22/Presidents-Update-February-22/</guid>
        
        
        <category>president-update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Modulo</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Helmet mounted motorcycle accessories and smart helmets are limited in functionality because of their need for power. Modulo is a helmet mounted device which provides constant power to all rider devices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Team Members&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Kiel Olver&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cobi Yu&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cyrus Larsen&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Katherine Wong&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Conor Macdonald&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Gabriela Roestandy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;This is a New Venture Design (NVD) project&lt;/h4&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/igen-project/2016/02/19/Modulo/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/igen-project/2016/02/19/Modulo/</guid>
        
        
        <category>IGEN-Project</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pro-Lock</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A programmable deadbolt lock, capable of using multiple keys. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Team Members&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Michael Harvey&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tom Smyth&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Greg Henderson&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/igen-project/2016/02/18/Pro-Lock/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/igen-project/2016/02/18/Pro-Lock/</guid>
        
        
        <category>IGEN-Project</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>High Radiation Vacuum Beamline Connection System</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The High Radiation Vacuum Beamline Connection System (HRVBCS) will streamline the process of changing vacuum seals and clamping beamlines for TRIUMF&#39;s ARIEL project. The HRVBCS will unclamp, remove the used seal from, place a new seal on, and re-clamp the beamline from a vertical distance of two meters. This shortens the seal change time by up to 80%, reducing time employees are exposed to harmful radiation and increasing the accuracy in which the seal is placed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Team Members&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Andrew Li&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Daniel Vecino Perez&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Danny George, Devin Husslage&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Felipe Luna, Ian Jones&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Kushagra Sharma&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tharesh Liyanage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://integratedengineers.ca/igen-project/2016/02/14/High-Radiation-Vacuum-Beamline-Connection-System/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://integratedengineers.ca/igen-project/2016/02/14/High-Radiation-Vacuum-Beamline-Connection-System/</guid>
        
        
        <category>IGEN-Project</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
